=Summer In Love=
= الصيف في الحب =
=Episode 10= (Don't Worry, No More Same Mistake)
= الحلقة 10 = (لا تقلق ، لا مزيد من الخطأ)
(Glad to meet you in Jiangbei) (Jiangbei University)
(سعيد بلقائك في جيانغبى) (جامعة جيانغبى)
(Jiangbei University welcomes students year 2008)
(ترحب جامعة جيانغبى بالطلاب عام 2008)
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Okay.
تمام.
(Shi Yi,)
(شي يي)
(you were my girlfriend before.)
(كنت صديقتي من قبل.)
(I can do the same now.)
(يمكنني أن أفعل الشيء نفسه الآن).
Why are we not driving?
لماذا لا نسوق؟
Must we walk?
هل يجب ان نسير؟
I don't want to
لا اريد
keep reminding myself
استمر في تذكير نفسي
that I don't belong to this world
أنني لا أنتمي إلى هذا العالم
because
لأن
I like the current us more.
أنا أحب الحالي لنا أكثر.
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
I
أنا
will sell the car
سيبيع السيارة
and
و
buy a bicycle for you,
شراء دراجة لك ،
okay?
تمام؟
It's a deal.
انها صفقة.
(Faculty of Arts Registration)
(تسجيل كلية الآداب)
Where should we register?
أين يجب أن نسجل؟
Over there.
هناك.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
We're freshmen.
نحن مبتدئون.
Do we register here?
هل نسجل هنا؟
Which faculty are you in?
في أي كلية أنت؟
Faculty of Arts.
كلية الفنون.
Faculty of Information Engineering.
كلية هندسة المعلومات.
Faculty of Information Engineering is there.
كلية هندسة المعلومات موجودة هناك.
I'll go register first.
سأذهب للتسجيل أولا.
Ill look for you later.
سأبحث عنك لاحقا.
Okay.
تمام.
Do you need my admission notice?
هل تحتاج إلى إشعار قبولي؟
Yes.
نعم.
(He has even come to the university.)
(لقد جاء حتى إلى الجامعة).
(He's just everywhere.)
(إنه في كل مكان فقط).
(Stop beating me!)
(توقف عن ضربي!)
I asked you here to give me ideas.
لقد طلبت منك هنا أن تعطيني أفكارًا.
I didn't ask you to look at him.
لم أطلب منك أن تنظر إليه.
You're useless.
أنت عديم الفائدة.
Why do you vent your anger on me?
لماذا تنفث عن غضبك علي؟
Let go.
اتركه.
Don't be mad.
لا تغضب.
I know you like Xia He,
أعرف أنك تحب شيا هي ،
but he only likes Shi Yi now.
لكنه يحب شي يي فقط الآن.
I'll make him like me.
سأجعله مثلي.
You better do.
من الافضل ان تفعل.
Our targets complement each other.
أهدافنا تكمل بعضها البعض.
You want Xia He.
تريد شيا هي.
I want Shi Yi.
اريد شي يي.
If you keep being so shameless,
إذا كنت لا تزال وقح جدا ،
more people will hate you.
سيكرهك المزيد من الناس.
Fine.
بخير.
You'll do it then.
ستفعل ذلك بعد ذلك.
I want to see how good you are.
اريد ان ارى كم انت جيد
Turn around.
التف حوله.
Are you tired?
هل أنت متعب؟
Here.
هنا.
Water.
ماء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Well, Shi Yi,
حسنًا ، شي يي ،
I have something
لدي شيئ ما
to tell you.
لإخبارك.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Xiaoyu looked for me
بحث شياويو عني
and said it's Gao Shanshan's birthday party tomorrow night.
وقالت انها حفلة عيد ميلاد جاو شانشان ليلة الغد.
She's invited me.
لقد دعتني.
Are you going?
هل انت ذاهب؟
I will go.
سأذهب.
I remember you say that
أتذكر أنك قلت ذلك
you got together
لقد اجتمعت
during the birthday party.
خلال حفلة عيد الميلاد.
That's why I'm going there
لهذا السبب أنا ذاهب إلى هناك
to break the relationship.
لقطع العلاقة.
Aren't you afraid...
ألا تخشى ...
I'm not.
أنالست.
I'm telling you
أنا أخبرك
so that you won't be worried.
حتى لا تقلق.
I...
أنا...
What's worrying me?
ما الذي يقلقني؟
Don't worry!
لا تقلق!
I won't make the same mistake.
لن أرتكب نفس الخطأ.
Let's get Xiaoyu to take a photo for us.
دعونا نجعل Xiaoyu يلتقط صورة لنا.
(Happy birthday to Gao Shanshan) Look at Xiaoyu.
(عيد ميلاد سعيد لغاو شانشان) انظر إلى شياويو.
Hold on.
(عيد ميلاد سعيد لغاو شانشان) انتظر.
(Happy birthday to Gao Shanshan) Let me find the angle.
(عيد ميلاد سعيد لغاو شانشان) دعني أجد الزاوية.
Okay.
تمام.
Thank you, Xiaoyu.
شكرا لك شياويو.
Here.
هنا.
Three,
ثلاثة،
two,
اثنين،
one.
واحد.
Xiaoyu, take a photo with us.
Xiaoyu ، التقط صورة معنا.
Come on.
تعال.
Don't treat me as an outsider.
لا تعاملني كغريب.
We were classmates in high school.
كنا زملاء الدراسة في المدرسة الثانوية.
Now, we're in the same faculty.
الآن ، نحن في نفس الكلية.
Don't be so formal.
لا تكن رسميًا جدًا.
I...
أنا...
I'll just take photo for you.
سآخذ صورة لك فقط.
No worries.
لا شكر على واجب.
Just sit down.
مجرد الجلوس.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's take a selfie.
لنأخذ صورة شخصية.
Here.
هنا.
Three,
ثلاثة،
two,
اثنين،
one.
واحد.
Look. How's it?
ينظر.  كيف حاله؟
Carry on.
حمل.
Xia He, you're here.
شيا هي ، أنت هنا.
Xia He,
شيا هي ،
I'm happy that you're here
أنا سعيد لأنك هنا
to my birthday celebration.
للاحتفال بعيد ميلادي.
When did they become so close?
متى أصبحوا قريبين جدا؟
I've never seen them together.
لم أرهم معًا أبدًا.
Maybe they do,
ربما يفعلون ،
but we don't know.
لكننا لا نعرف.
Shanshan is beautiful
شانشان جميلة
and her family is wealthy.
وعائلتها ثرية.
Why would she fall in love
لماذا ستقع في الحب
with Xia He?
مع شيا هي؟
(Where's Shi Yi?)
(أين شي يي؟)
(Xia He's here.)
(شيا هو هنا.)
(Why is she not here?)
(لماذا هي ليست هنا؟)
My waist is wasted.
خصري ضائع.
I want to take leave tomorrow.
اريد ان اخذ اجازة غدا.
Shi Yi, are you not tired?
شي يي ، أنت لست متعب؟
I'm tired,
أنا متعب،
but I'm happy.
لكن انا سعيد.
Why are you happy?
لماذا انت سعيد؟
Go back first.
العودة أولا.
- Bye.
- الوداع.  - الوداع.
We'll go up first.
سنصعد أولاً.
Hello, Xiaoyu.
مرحبا شياويو.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Hello, Shi Yi.
مرحبا شي يي.
Why didn't you come to
لماذا لم تأت إلى
Gao Shanshan's birthday party?
حفلة عيد ميلاد جاو شانشان؟
She didn't invite me.
لم تدعوني.
No way.
مستحيل.
She told me that
قالت لي ذلك
she's invited you.
لقد دعتك.
Also,
أيضًا،
she asked me to get Xia He here as well.
طلبت مني أن أحضر شيا هي هنا أيضًا.
No worries.
لا شكر على واجب.
Anyways, I don't want to go.
على أي حال ، لا أريد الذهاب.
Did you
هل فعلت
see Xia He?
ترى شيا هي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
Many people that I don't know
كثير من الناس الذين لا أعرفهم
are forcing him to drink.
تجبره على الشرب.
Help me take a look at him.
ساعدني في إلقاء نظرة عليه.
Ask him to drink lesser.
اطلب منه أن يشرب أقل.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll help you.
سوف اساعدك.
I don't mean that.
لا أقصد ذلك.
I mean I...
اقصد اني...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
I'm hanging up.
سأغلق السماعة.
Come on.
تعال.
(Girls Dorm Building Two)
(مبنى سكن البنات الثاني)
Can you stop looking for me?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن البحث عني؟
I know what you're thinking.
أنا أعرف ما كنت أفكر.
Let me tell you clearly.
دعني أخبرك بوضوح.
I don't like you.
أنا لا أحبك.
Don't make a fool out of yourself.
لا تخدع نفسك.
Go away.
يبتعد.
(Girls Dorm Building Two)
(مبنى سكن البنات الثاني)
You used
استخدمته
to be gentle to me.
ليكون لطيفا معي.
You're...
أنت على...
Dear,
عزيزي،
we met again.
التقينا مرة أخرى.